<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Carleton Coffrin</title>
    <link>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Carleton Coffrin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography Carleton Coffrin is a staff scientist in Los Alamos National Laboratory&amp;rsquo;s Advanced Network Science Initiative. His research interests focus on how optimization algorithms can be applied to applications on infrastructure networks. His background spans many forms of optimization including mathematical programing, constraint programming, and local search. Recently Carleton has been exploring online learning via open-online courses and youtube videos as well was novel computing architectures such as, quantum computers, neuromorphic computers and memristors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Publications</title>
      <link>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/publications_selected/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/publications_selected/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Software</title>
      <link>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/software/</guid>
      <description> PowerModels.jl: a Julia package for Power Network optimization Juniper.jl: a nonlinear branch-and-bound JuMP solver for finding feasible solutions to non-convex mixed-integer nonlinear programs ac-opf-bounds: a python tool for optimization-based bound tightening on power network datasets DWIG: a python tool for generating test cases for D-Wave quantum computer STAC: a web-based tool for visualization for power network datasets grg-mpdata: python parsers and data structures for Matpower data files  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Courses Co-Instructor with Pascal Van Hentenryck, Discrete Optimization (delivered by Coursera) Melbourne University, Melbourne, VIC, 2013 - Present
Co-Instructor with Peter Stuckey, Modeling for Discrete Optimization (delivered by Coursera) Melbourne University, Melbourne, VIC, 2015
Teaching Assistant for Peter Stuckey, Modeling for Discrete Optimization (COMP90046) Melbourne University, Melbourne, VIC, 2014 and 2015
Graduate Teaching Assistant for Claire Mathieu, Design and Analysis of Algorithms (CSCI1570) Brown University, Providence, RI, 2010 and 2012</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Activities</title>
      <link>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/other/</guid>
      <description>Awards Los Alamos National Laboratory 2019 Distinguished Performance Award for Critical Infrastructure Optimization Software
Los Alamos National Laboratory 2018 LAAP Award for Leadership in the Quantum Computation Summer School
Los Alamos National Laboratory 2018 LAAP Award for C2S Development Efforts
Los Alamos National Laboratory 2017 LAAP Award for Exploration of Quantum Computation
Los Alamos National Laboratory 2017 Early Career Researcher Award for Large-Scale Nonlinear Optimization via Cloud Computing
PES 2014, Application of Modern Heuristic Optimization Algorithms for Solving Optimal Power Flow Problems, finalist (1 of 5), for Heuristic MINLP for Optimal Power Flow Problems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ccoffrin.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>